<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BehaviourDrivenDevelopment on BDD Wiki</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in BehaviourDrivenDevelopment on BDD Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NonFunctionalRequirements</title><link>/nonfunctionalrequirements/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 20:19:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>/nonfunctionalrequirements/</guid><description/></item><item><title>TechnicalStories</title><link>/technicalstories/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 20:17:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>/technicalstories/</guid><description/></item><item><title>SoftwareIndustryRecordOfFailure</title><link>/softwareindustryrecordoffailure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 20:05:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>/softwareindustryrecordoffailure/</guid><description/></item><item><title>WheresTheBusinessValue</title><link>/wheresthebusinessvalue/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 20:04:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>/wheresthebusinessvalue/</guid><description>Every behaviour of a system should be there because it adds concretely to the business value of the system as a whole.
All too often software projects gain some kind of perverse impetus of their own, where features are added or technologies are chosen because they are &amp;ldquo;cool&amp;rdquo; or because the technical folk associated with the project feel that they are protecting their sponsors against some possible future requirements that the sponsors haven&amp;rsquo;t thought of or considered yet.</description></item><item><title>ItsAllBehaviour</title><link>/itsallbehaviour/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 20:03:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>/itsallbehaviour/</guid><description>Or more accurately, it&amp;rsquo;s all about what a system should do. BehaviourDrivenDevelopment is all about GettingTheWordsRight. We find that when we use a consistent vocabulary, much of the traditional disconnect between Business and Technology simply disappears.
Defining a system in terms of its behaviour works because it has different meanings at different levels of abstraction.</description></item><item><title>AcceptanceTestDrivenPlanning</title><link>/acceptancetestdrivenplanning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 19:56:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>/acceptancetestdrivenplanning/</guid><description/></item><item><title>UbiquitousLanguage</title><link>/ubiquitouslanguage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 17:55:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ubiquitouslanguage/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DomainDrivenDesign</title><link>/domaindrivendesign/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 17:52:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>/domaindrivendesign/</guid><description>Domain Driven Design is an approach to software design that focusses on the strengths of OO software development techniques to simulate the core of the problem at hand.
At its core it concentrates on building a simulation of the problem domain, minimizing technical influences, and attempting also to minimize misunderstandings between users of the software and the developers by establishing and using a common vocabulary (aka UbiquitousLanguage).
This approach has been in use by experienced programmers for many years, but has gained more prominence recently because of Eric Evans' excellent book by the same name.</description></item><item><title>TestDrivenDevelopment</title><link>/testdrivendevelopment/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 17:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>/testdrivendevelopment/</guid><description>Test Driven Development (aka TDD) is a programming technique that encourages an evolutionary approach to the design and development of a system.
It encourages programmers to write tests before they write the code that the tests interact with as a means of focusing the programmer&amp;rsquo;s attention on the problem that they are intending to solve rather than on the solution. This has many positive outcomes.
TDD is often associated with ExtremeProgramming.</description></item></channel></rss>